clickview.com.au 2015-06-21

# Privacy Policy - ClickView

ClickView Pty Limited and its subsidiaries (we, our, us) recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of those who visit or use ClickView. ClickView understands and appreciates that you, as a ClickView user, are concerned about the confidentiality and security of information ClickView may collect about you. When we collect information from you, we want you to know how it is used.

#### What information does ClickView gather?

We collect personal information such as name, mailing or street address, email address, telephone number, details of products that you have purchased from us or enquired about, information you provide to our customer service team, customer surveys, promotional codes, payment method details, confirmation of your Screenright’s licence and billing information when you knowingly provide it to us Our Web servers may automatically collect statistical information about your visit such as pages visited and which browsers are used to visit our site. None of this information is associated with you as an individual (see information about cookies). If collected, we would use these statistics to monitor our site's performance and to make it user-friendly.

#### What happens when I provide personal information on this Website and Products?

We collect your personal information directly from you unless it is unreasonable or impracticable to do so. When collecting personal information from you, we may collect in ways including:

  * Through your access and use of our website;
  * Through your access and use of our products;
  * During conversations between you and the ClickView team; or
  * When you complete a transaction

When you supply information for a specific purpose such as ordering a product or service from ClickView, we use the information only for the purpose of providing that product or service and ongoing support.

#### What happens when I provide information to subscribe to ClickView?

When you subscribe with ClickView, we request accurate contact information for your school and staff. This is used to provide ongoing product support and to send you company and product information, special offers and/or newsletters.

If you're a ClickView customer, we store your name, purchase and usage history and billing information to allow us to continue to provide support and training.

In order to improve your experience with us, we may decide to improve our site's ability to obtain information about users. If we do, we will update this privacy statement continually to ensure that you are aware of developments in this area.

#### For what purpose do we collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information?

We require your information for the purposes of:

  * Providing products and services to you and to send communications requested by you;
  * Answering enquiries and provide information or advice about existing and new products or services;
  * Administrative, marketing (including direct marketing), planning, product or service development, quality assurance;
  * Billing purposes including invoicing and accounts receivable;
  * Complying with any law, rule, regulation, lawful and binding determination, decision or direction of a regulator, or in co-operation with any governmental authority of any country; and
  * To provide member and service user support.

ClickView will endeavour to take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, up to date and relevant. Please contact ClickView should you need to update your information.

#### To whom may we disclose your information?

We may disclose your personal information to:

  * Our employees, fulfilling requests by you, and to otherwise provide products and services to you including, without limitation, web hosting providers, mailing houses, couriers, payment processors;
  * Suppliers and other third parties with whom we have commercial relationships, for business, hardware, marketing, and related purposes; and
  * Any organisation for any authorised purpose with your express consent.

As we care about your person information, we do not share any personally identifiable data that we collect from you with information collected by any of external providers (within Australia) unless you have consented to the use or disclosure of the information. Please note that all of our data centres in Australia (that host ClickView Exchange, Media Store, ClickView 24-7 Cloud and customer database) do not have access to your personal information. 

We may disclose non-personally identifiable information to third party service providers managed by Microsoft Corporation Limited for hosting of ClickView Online. Microsoft Corporation Limited and ClickView continue to work together to ensure that we meet the privacy provisions of Australian Privacy Principle 8. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the overseas recipients of this information do not breach the privacy obligations relating to your data.

#### How often will you contact me? 

ClickView may contact you for the purposes of product, technical or billing purposes. We will contact you directly if you’re a current user of the product, or you have provided your details to us and you have not requested to unsubscribe. If you would not like to receive any further communications in relation to the respective topic, please email us at info@clickview.com.au or follow the prompts in the electronic direct marketing that you have received to unsubscribe. Please note that ClickView ensures that it will not contact students for the purposes of direct marketing.

#### How can you access and correct your personal information?

You may request access to any personal information we hold about you at any time by contacting us (see the details below). Where we hold information that you are entitled to access, we will try to provide you with suitable means of accessing it (for example, by mailing or emailing it to you). If you believe that personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, then you may request us to amend it. 

There may be instances where we cannot grant you access to the personal information we hold. For example, we may need to refuse access if granting access would interfere with the privacy of others or if it would result in a breach of confidentiality (12.3(b) of the Australian Privacy Principles). If that happens, we will give you written reasons for any refusal.

#### Do you sell or give my information to other companies?

No, we do not sell individually identifiable information obtained online about our visitors to anyone. The only exception to this rule is if we are required by law to release information.

If you provide individually identifiable information at an event that we sponsor with another company, or if you subscribe or register on a co-sponsored or co-branded website and products, you may be providing the individually identifiable information to the co-sponsor. Review the privacy statement on the co-branded site to learn how the partner uses this information. Be assured that we use this information in accordance with this privacy policy.

On occasion, ClickView shares non-personally identifiable information with other companies in order to assess the results of a promotion. This information is used in aggregate only, and does not contain any information that would personally identify you. Information could be shared with an authorised ClickView reseller to fulfil a request for information or to follow up on an inquiry.

Personal information submitted to ClickView may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which ClickView its affiliates or authorised resellers maintain offices. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of ClickView. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties.

#### What about cookies?

In some cases we may also collect your personal information through the use of cookies. When you access our website, we may send a “cookie” (which is a small summary file containing a unique ID number) to your computer. This enables us to recognise your computer and greet you each time you visit our website without bothering you with a request to register/login. It also enables us to keep track of products or services you view so that, if you consent, we can send you news about those products or services.

We also use cookies to measure traffic patterns, to determine which areas of our website have been visited and to measure transaction patterns in the aggregate. We use this to research our users’ habits so that we can improve our online products and services. Our cookies do not collect personal information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser so that your computer does not accept them. Please note if your browser is set to not accept cookies, you will not be able to use our site or service.

We may log IP addresses (that is, the electronic addresses of computers connected to the internet) to analyse trends, administer the website, track users movements, and gather broad demographic information.

#### What do you do with personally identifiable information?

Personal information you voluntarily supply when obtaining information, purchasing services or interacting with our advertising may be shared with authorised resellers or affiliates of ClickView. Should any changes be made in the way we use personally identifiable information, ClickView will contact you via email notifying you of this change and give you the opportunity to choose to opt out of such use.

#### How do you protect my personal information?

We are committed to protecting the information you give us, so we implement the appropriate safeguards to do so. Within ClickView your information is stored in password-protected, limited-access servers. Wherever possible, ClickView servers reside behind a firewall that maintains tight controls on any access to the system from both our internal network and the Internet. Employees are made aware of our privacy policy and are trained on procedures to handle privacy-related concerns.

We take reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is protected from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. Personal information is destroyed or de-identified when no longer needed.

As ClickView’s website and applications are linked to the internet, and as the internet is inherently insecure, we cannot provide any assurance regarding the security of transmission of information you communicate to us online. We also cannot guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the internet. Accordingly, any personal information or other information which you transmit to us online is transmitted at your own risk.

#### What is the process for complaining about a breach of privacy?

If you believe that your privacy has been breached, please contact us using the contact information below and provide details of the incident so that we can investigate it.

Our procedure for investigating and dealing with privacy breaches is:

Step 1: On discovery of any privacy breach that involves you we will contain the breach and escalate to the appropriate department to investigate.

Step 2: We will notify you of the outcome within a reasonable time.

Step 3: We will undertake best endeavours to prevent future breaches by making any necessary changes to processes.

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, any concerns or a complaint regarding the treatment of your privacy or a possible breach of your privacy, please contact us at [info@clickview.com.au](mailto:info@clickview.com.au)
